When masters unite a new legacy begins.
Karate Kid: Legends is a action, adventure, drama
film directed by Jonathan Entwistle.
After a family tragedy, kung fu prodigy Li Fong is uprooted from his home in
Beijing and forced to move to New York City with his mother.
When a new friend needs his help, Li enters a karate
competition – but his skills alone aren't enough.
Li's kung fu teacher Mr.
Han enlists original Karate Kid Daniel LaRusso for help, and Li learns a new way to fight,
merging their two styles into one for the ultimate martial arts showdown.
Mr. Han, played by Jackie Chan.
Li Fong, played by Ben Wang.
Victor Lipani, played by Joshua Jackson.
Mia Lipani, played by Sadie Stanley.
Dr. Fong, played by Ming-Na Wen.
Alan, played by Wyatt Oleff.
Karate Kid: Legends is a 2025 American martial arts drama film starring Jackie
Chan and Ralph Macchio, while introducing Ben Wang as the main lead.
It is the sixth film in The Karate Kid franchise, serving as a follow-up to The
Karate Kid (2010) and the television series Cobra Kai (2018–2025).
Both Chan and Macchio reprise their roles from the franchise—the latter's first
involvement in a film from the franchise since The Karate Kid Part III (1989).
The story follows Li (Wang), a kung fu prodigy who, after moving to New York and
confronting a local karate champion, receives help from his former master Mr.
Han (Chan) and karate sensei Daniel LaRusso (Macchio).
It is the first film in the series not to be produced
by Jerry Weintraub, who died in 2015.
The film was confirmed to be in development in September 2022, with Jonathan Entwistle
set to direct and Rob Lieber set to write the screenplay in November 2023.
Casting took place from November 2023 to April 2024.
Principal photography took place from April to June 2024.
Karate Kid: Legends premiered at the Cinépolis Mitikah in Mexico City, Mexico on May 7, 2025,
and was released in the United States by Sony Pictures Releasing on May 30.
It received mixed reviews from critics and has grossed $117 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of new york city, martial
arts, kung fu, mentor, ex-boyfriend.
The tone is emotional.